Michelle Brytowski

Junior Web Developer

Westminster, CO 80234 (612) 554-1529 mn.brytowski@gmail.com

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/michelle-brytowski-98505b50

Profile: https://mbrytowski.github.io/FinalPortfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/MBrytowski

CAREER STATEMENT

MERN Full-Stack Developer with attention to detail and ability to debug HTML, CSS & Javascript. Creating a website or application that is both user friendly and aesthetically pleasing are goals that drive my work. My past experience has shown that I learn roles quickly and am given added responsibilities shortly after being given new positions. My six months spent in the Web Development Bootcamp through the University of Denver have given me the skills to hit the ground running in a Junior Developer position.

SKILLS

MERN Full-stack training: HTML, CSS, JavaScript including jQuery and Node.js.

EXPERIENCE

FirstBank, Lakewood, CO - Commercial Loan Coordinator

JANUARY 2016 - PRESENT

- Researching non-standard collateral to meet bank requirements.
- Collaborating with officers and loan staff to prepare loan documents.

FirstBank, Lakewood, CO - Credit Card Representative

MARCH 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

- Assisted branch and corporate personnel with Credit Card maintenance.
- Completed Monthly and Quarterly Reporting reports and documents.

Starbucks, Louisville, CO - Barista

OCTOBER 2013 - MARCH 2014

- Prepared beverages and pastries to customer specifications.
- Supported management with other miscellaneous tasks throughout the store.

EDUCATION

University of Denver, Web Development Bootcamp, Denver, CO - Certificate

September 2018 - April 2019

MERN Full-Stack Training

North Dakota State University, Fargo, ND - Bachelor of Science

August 2004 - December 2010

B.S in Radiologic Science, two-year immersive technical training at Avera McKennan Hospital included; Minor in Chemistry